Wauregan and Quinebaug Company Records 1981.0010
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VI: Labor Records, 1855-1958
  - Subseries C: Personnel Files, 1936-1958
    - LePage, Arthur, Jr., 1951 (Box 221:3459)
    - LePage, Elsie E. House, 1952 (Box 221:3460)
    - LePage, George, 1948 (Box 221:3460a)
    - Lepak, Aniela, 1944 (Box 221:3461)
    - Lernould, Henri J., 1940 (Box 221:3462)
    - Lesage, Albert J., 1941 (Box 221:3463)
    - Lesage, Henry J., 1937 (Box 221:3464)
    - Lesage, Loretta, 1943 (Box 221:3465)
    - Lesage, Madeleine C. Deloge, 1940 (Box 221:3466)
    - Lesnak, Katherine, 1939 (Box 221:3467)
    - L'Esperance, Arthur, 1942 (Box 221:3468)
    - Lessard, Delphis, 1941 (Box 221:3469)
    - Lessard, Roderick G., 1941 (Box 221:3470)
    - Lessard, Romeo R., 1941 (Box 221:3471)
    - Lester, Henry E., Jr., 1942 (Box 221:3472)
    - Lester, Henry F., 1953 (Box 221:3473)
    - Lester, Patrick, 1945 (Box 221:3474)
    - Letoile, Clara Trudell, 1942 (Box 221:3475)
    - L'Etoile, Joseph, 1956 (Box 221:3476)
    - Lever, Martha H., 1951 (Box 221:3477)
    - Lever, Viola L. Czmya, 1942 (Box 221:3478)
    - Levesque, Alexina B., 1939 (Box 221:3479)
    - Levesque, Bertha S., 1940 (Box 221:3480)
    - Levesque, Delia M. Bishop, 1952 (Box 221:3481)
    - Levesque, Dona, 1941 (Box 221:3482)
    - Levesque, Donald A., 1943 (Box 221:3483)
    - Levesque, Ferdinand, 1937 (Box 221:3484)
    - Levesque, Florent R., 1949 (Box 221:3485)
    - Levesque, Henry A., 1937 (Box 221:3486)
    - Levesque, Henry J., 1939 (Box 221:3487)
    - Levesque, Irene M. H., 1949 (Box 221:3488)
    - Levesque, Louis J., 1941 (Box 221:3489)
    - Levesque, Mary A. Zercie, 1945 (Box 221:3490)
    - Levesque, Peter, 1941 (Box 221:3491)
    - Levesque, Raoul A., 1942 (Box 221:3492)
    - Levesque, Rejeanne, 1956 (Box 221:3493)
    - Levesque, Wilbrod, 1956 (Box 221:3494)
    - Lewis, Angelo P., 1942 (Box 221:3495)
    - Lewis Della, 1950 (Box 221:3496)
    - Lewis, George F., 1952 (Box 221:3497)
    - Lewis, Harold J., 1951 (Box 221:3498)
    - Lewis, Janet, 1952 (Box 221:3499)
    - Lewis, Mary, 1937 (Box 221:3500)
    - Lewis, Nicholas, 1939 (Box 221:3501)
    - Lewis, Roland, 1954 (Box 221:3502)
    - Lewis, William, 1938 (Box 221:3503)
    - L'Heureux, Donald Joseph, 1942 (Box 221:3504)
    - L'Heureux, Henry, 1940 (Box 221:3505)
    - L'Heureux, Richard E., 1939 (Box 221:3506)
    - L'Heureux, Robert P., 1939 (Box 221:3507)
    - L'Homme, Leda Lafleur, 1941 (Box 221:3508)
    - Liguz, Anna P., 1941 (Box 221:3509)
    - Lillibridge, Alice, 1950 (Box 221:3510)
    - Lime, Arthur, 1946 (Box 221:3511)
    - Lincoln, Charlotte, 1942 (Box 221:3512)
    - Lindberg, Mertice, 1954 (Box 221:3513)
    - Lippe, Armand, 1949 (Box 221:3514)
    - Lippe, Gerard, 1950 (Box 221:3515)
    - Lippe, Paul H., 1951 (Box 221:3516)
    - Lippiello, Victor E., 1956 (Box 221:3517)
    - Lisee, Alphonse, 1939 (Box 221:3518)
    - Lisee, Jerry Arthur, 1942 (Box 221:3519)
    - Livernoche, Lillian, 1942 (Box 221:3520)
    - Llivernoche, Ovila J., 1938 (Box 221:3521)
    - Lockhart, Lucille, 1955 (Box 221:3522)
    - Loiselle, John, Jr., 1951 (Box 221:3523)
    - Loiselle, John, Sr., 1951 (Box 221:3524)
    - Loiselle, Irene Rose, 1944 (Box 221:3525)
    - Loiselle, Joseph Deneige Fortunat, 1937 (Box 221:3526)
    - Lollis, James T>, 1950 (Box 221:3527)
    - Lombardy, Louis, 1953 (Box 221:3528)
    - Lombardy, William J., 1952 (Box 221:3529)
    - Long, Clarence, 1948 (Box 221:3530)
    - Long, Clarence E., Jr., 1939 (Box 221:3531)
    - Long, Herbert L., 1956 (Box 221:3532)
    - Long, Theresa T., 1952 (Box 221:3533)
    - Longo, Anna E., 1940 (Box 221:3534)
    - Longo, Marion A., 1940 (Box 221:3535)
    - Loomis, Craig, Albert, 1950 (Box 221:3536)
    - Lopriore, Peter M., 1955 (Box 221:3537)
    - Lorello, Eva Richard, 1940 (Box 221:3538)
    - Louby, John, 1943 (Box 221:3539)
    - Louthis, Leonidas, 1949 (Box 221:3540)
    - Lovering, Everett P., 1952 (Box 221:3541)
    - Lubowicz, Kazimierz, 1937 (Box 221:3542)
    - Lucas, George F., 1938 (Box 221:3543)
    - Lucibella, Albert, 1937 (Box 221:3544)
    - Lucibella, Frank, 1937 (Box 221:3545)
    - Lucier, Edward J., 1939 (Box 221:3546)
    - Lucier, Helen M., 1952 (Box 221:3547)
    - Lucier, Rita, 1954 (Box 221:3548)
    - Luis, Evelyn, 1957 (Box 221:3549)
    - Lukin, Mate, 1954 (Box 221:3550)
    - Lukin, Christie T., 1940 (Box 221:3551)
    - Lupa, Katarcena N., 1939 (Box 221:3552)
    - Luppert, Harold, 1950 (Box 221:3553)
    - Lussier, Dorothy, 1955 (Box 221:3554)
    - Lussier, Edward, 1956 (Box 221:3555)
    - Lussier, Eva, 1946 (Box 221:3556)
    - Luszcyk, Bernice, 1948 (Box 221:3557)
    - Lyday, Henry W., 1941 (Box 221:3558)
    - Macha, David J., 1939 (Box 221:3559)
    - Mack, Louise A. R., 1937 (Box 221:3560)
    - Mackie, John, 1956 (Box 221:3561)
    - Macomber, George W., 1942 (Box 221:3562)
    - Macomber, Mary, 1951 (Box 221:3563)
    - Madden, James C., 1955 (Box 221:3564)
    - Magao, Virginia A., 1957 (Box 221:3565)
    - Magrey, Harriet Bernice, 1950 (Box 221:3566)
    - Maguder, Mary, 1947 (Box 221:3567)
    - Mailhot, Clara, 1939 (Box 221:3568)
    - Mailloux, Dora E. B., 1938 (Box 221:3569)
    - Mailloux, George E., 1938 (Box 221:3570)
    - Mailloux, Philip, 1957 (Box 221:3571)
    - Mailloux, Roger, 1956 (Box 221:3572)
    - Mailloux, Theresa Deviney, 1949 (Box 221:3573)
    - Main, Carl A., 1953 (Box 221:3574)
    - Main, George, 1950 (Box 221:3575)
    - Main, Thomas, 1953 (Box 221:3576)
    - Maine, Charles Vernon, 1947 (Box 221:3577)
    - Mainville, Arthur A., 1939 (Box 221:3578)
    - Mainville, Marie, 1947 (Box 221:3579)
    - Major, Conrad, Sr., 1947 (Box 221:3580)
    - Maki, Ida, 1942 (Box 221:3582)
    - Makuch, Peter, 1950 (Box 221:3583)
    - Malboeuf, Dorothy H. Staskivitch, 1944 (Box 221:3584)
    - Malboeuf, Lillian, 1945 (Box 221:3585)
    - Malboeuf, Meddie R., 1953 (Box 221:3586)
    - Malboeuf, Robert, 1949 (Box 221:3587)
    - Malcoon, Marielle L., 1953 (Box 221:3588)
    - Malo, Albert, 1939 (Box 221:3589)
    - Malo, Alexander, 1957 (Box 221:3590)
    - Malo, Henry Norman, 1946 (Box 221:3591)
    - Malo, Florence B., 1941 (Box 221:3592)
    - Malone, Frank Anthony, 1947 (Box 221:3593)
    - Maloney, Edward D., 1942 (Box 221:3594)
    - Malsz, Mary, 1942 (Box 221:3595)
    - Mandeville, Alfred J., 1955 (Box 221:3596)
    - Mandeville, Alfred Leon, 1955 (Box 221:3597)
    - Mandeville, Anita, 1957 (Box 221:3598)
    - Mandeville, Arthur, 1949 (Box 221:3599)
    - Mandeville, Blanche S., 1941 (Box 221:3600)
    - Mandeville, Eva M. L., 1943 (Box 221:3601)
    - Mandeville, Henry J., 1956 (Box 221:3602)
    - Mandeville, Joseph, 1940 (Box 221:3603)
    - Mandeville, Lucien, 1957 (Box 221:3604)
    - Mandeville, Paul H., 1937 (Box 221:3605)
    - Mandeville, Rosario L., 1951 (Box 221:3606)
    - Mandeville, Theodore, 1941 (Box 221:3607)
    - Manso, Paul, 1949 (Box 221:3608)
    - Manville, Alfred, 1943 (Box 221:3609)
    - Marcaurelle, Armand A., 1942 (Box 221:3610)
    - Marcaurelle, Lydia B., 1942 (Box 221:3611)
    - Marcaurelle, Urban A., 1941 (Box 221:3612)
    - Marcelina, Eva B., 1940 (Box 221:3613)
    - Marchesseault, Henry, Jr., 1940 (Box 221:3614)
    - Marchesseault, Lucien, 1945 (Box 221:3615)
    - Marchessault, Norman, 1952 (Box 221:3616)
    - Marcotte, Ludger J., 1951 (Box 221:3617)
    - Marcure, Hilda, 1949 (Box 221:3618)
    - Marcure, Joseph C., 1940 (Box 221:3619)
    - Marion, Eugenie D., 1952 (Box 221:3620)
    - Marois, Edmond J., 1955 (Box 221:3621)
    - Marois, Rosario J., 1937 (Box 221:3622)
    - Marois, Simonne G., 1941 (Box 221:3623)
    - Marquis, Paul, 1941 (Box 221:3624)
    - Marrotte, John, 1948 (Box 221:3625)
    - Marsh, Elmer, 1942 (Box 221:3626)
    - Marshall, Clarinda F., 1939 (Box 221:3627)
    - Marshall, Gertrude, 1942 (Box 221:3628)
    - Marshall, Joseph, 1942 (Box 221:3629)
    - Marshall, William J., Jr., 1939 (Box 221:3630)
    - Marszalek, Gertrude M. P., 1942 (Box 221:3631)
    - Marszalek, John M., 1955 (Box 221:3632)
    - Marszalek, Kunegunda, 1943 (Box 221:3633)
    - Marszalek, Mary M., 1944 (Box 221:3634)
    - Marszalek, Walter, 1951 (Box 221:3635)
    - Martakis, Apostolos, 1951 (Box 221:3636)
    - Martel, Alcide, 1947 (Box 221:3637)
    - Martel, Alfred J., 1940 (Box 221:3638)
    - Martel, Earl Lawrence, 1947 (Box 221:3639)
    - Martel, Edward J., 1939 (Box 221:3640)
    - Martel, Isabelle D., 1951 (Box 221:3641)
    - Martel, Lionel, 1956 (Box 221:3642)
    - Martel, M. I. Rolande, 1950 (Box 221:3643)
    - Martel, Mary L., 1937 (Box 221:3644)
    - Martel, Pauline, 1947 (Box 221:3645)
    - Martel, Renald, 1953 (Box 221:3646)
    - Martell, Ronald, 1955 (Box 221:3647)
    - Martica, James J., 1942 (Box 221:3648)
    - Martica, Lulu H., 1941 (Box 221:3649)
    - Martin, Arthur J., Jr., 1950 (Box 221:3650)
    - Martin, Arthur J., Sr., 1950 (Box 221:3651)
    - Martin, August, 1941 (Box 221:3652)
    - Martin, Bella, 1955 (Box 221:3653)
    - Martin, Frank, 1947 (Box 221:3654)
    - Martin, John, 1943 (Box 221:3655)
    - Martin, Joseph L., 1941 (Box 221:3656)
    - Martin, Laura Letender, 1940 (Box 221:3657)
    - Martin, Mabel C., 1953 (Box 221:3658)
    - Martin, Mary Jane, 1941 (Box 221:3659)
    - Martin, Paul J., 1940 (Box 221:3660)
    - Martine, Frank, 1943 (Box 221:3661)
    - Martine, Michael, 1942 (Box 221:3662)
    - Mason, Gerald M., 1941 (Box 221:3663)
    - Masse, Edward C., 1939 (Box 221:3664)
    - Masse, George A., 1937 (Box 221:3665)
    - Masse, Jules, 1949 (Box 221:3666)
    - Masson, Josaphat F., 1943 (Box 221:3667)
    - Masson, Mary, 1946 (Box 221:3668)
    - Mathieu, Blanche D. D., 1954 (Box 221:3669)
    - Mathieu, George, 1953 (Box 221:3670)
    - Mathieu, Lucille R., 1952 (Box 221:3671)
    - Mathieu, William H., 1940 (Box 221:3672)
    - Mathurin, Joseph J., 1942 (Box 222:3673)
    - Mathurin, Montcalm, 1942 (Box 222:3674)
    - Mattson, John, 1943 (Box 222:3675)
    - Matteau, Omer, 1950 (Box 222:3676)
    - Matthews, Odessa, 1942 (Box 222:3677)
    - Maurice, Raymond V., 1939 (Box 222:3678)
    - Mayhew, Earl E., 1941 (Box 222:3679)
    - Mayhew, Celia S., 1954 (Box 222:3680)
    - Mayhew, Rose A., 1938 (Box 222:3681)
    - Maynard, Agnes, 1951 (Box 222:3682)
    - Maynard, Antoinette F., 1940 (Box 222:3683)
    - Maynard, Constance B., 1956 (Box 222:3684)
    - Maynard, Donald W., 1942 (Box 222:3685)
    - Maynard, Ernest R., 1940 (Box 222:3686)
    - Maynard, Laurent M., 1940 (Box 222:3687)
    - Maynard, Leo E., 1939 (Box 222:3688)
    - Maynard, Lila, 1942 (Box 222:3689)
    - Maynard, Lucienne, 1953 (Box 222:3690)
    - Maynard, Yvonne L., 1948 (Box 222:3691)
    - Mayo, Dora, 1955 (Box 222:3692)
    - Mayo, Frank, 1956 (Box 222:3693)
    - Mazgay, Joseph, 1951 (Box 222:3694)
    - Maziarz, Henryka P., 1939 (Box 222:3695)
    - Mazzarella, Adrien, 1938 (Box 222:3696)
    - Mazzarella, Anna M. G., 1947 (Box 222:3697)
    - Mazzarella, Constantino, 1941 (Box 222:3698)
    - Mazzarella, Florian, 1945 (Box 222:3699)
    - Mazzarella, Joseph S., 1950 (Box 222:3700)
    - Meador, Betty, 1951 (Box 222:3701)
    - Medberry, Roseanna, 1942 (Box 222:3702)
    - Medeiros, Rena, 1946 (Box 222:3703)
    - Meinhold, Katherine M., 1956 (Box 222:3704)
    - Melanson, Jeanette, 1942 (Box 222:3705)
    - Melanson, Leon, 1947 (Box 222:3706)
    - Melanson, Samuel, 1940 (Box 222:3707)
    - Menard, Ernest L., 1941 (Box 222:3708)
    - Menard, Leo J., 1953 (Box 222:3709)
    - Menard, Napoleon, 1955 (Box 222:3710)
    - Mercer, George D., 1947 (Box 222:3711)
    - Mercer, Loretta B., 1940 (Box 222:3712)
    - Mercier, Agnes Flagg, 1944 (Box 222:3713)
    - Mercier, Henry J., 1952 (Box 222:3714)
    - Mercier, Irene, 1940 (Box 222:3715)
    - Mercier, Isidore W., 1938 (Box 222:3716)
    - Mercier, Julia, 1946 (Box 222:3717)
    - Mercier, Peter, 1939 (Box 222:3718)
    - Mercier, Samuel, 1941 (Box 222:3719)
    - Mercier, Simonne B. Robert, 1940 (Box 222:3720)
    - Mercier, Wilfred L., 1939 (Box 222:3721)
    - Mercier, William P., 1956 (Box 222:3722)
    - Messier, Armand H., 1940 (Box 222:3723)
    - Messier, Arthur C., 1938 (Box 222:3724)
    - Messier, Arthur H., 1952 (Box 222:3725)
    - Messier, Bernadette Beaydreau Belanger, 1956 (Box 222:3726)
    - Messier, Gerard A., 1956 (Box 222:3727)
    - Messier, Ida, 1952 (Box 222:3728)
    - Messier, Joseph, 1941 (Box 222:3729)
    - Messier, Juliette E., 1939 (Box 222:3730)
    - Messier, Malvina Plankey, 1955 (Box 222:3731)
    - Messier, Malvina Pope, 1954 (Box 222:3732)
    - Messier, Mathias, 1956 (Box 222:3733)
    - Messier, Mathias, Jr., 1946 (Box 222:3734)
    - Messier, Maurice, 1956 (Box 222:3735)
    - Messier, Polydor, 1956 (Box 222:3736)
    - Messier, Rene, 1943 (Box 222:3737)
    - Messier, Roseflore, 1945 (Box 222:3738)
    - Messier, Viola, 1942 (Box 222:3739)
    - Methot, Amanda L., 1939 (Box 222:3740)
    - Methot, Charles E., 1941 (Box 222:3741)
    - Methot, Edward H., 1941 (Box 222:3742)
    - Methot, Lawrence, 1953 (Box 222:3743)
    - Methot, Rita T., 1951 (Box 222:3744)
    - Metras, Ezare, 1939 (Box 222:3745)
    - Metthe, Oliva, 1942 (Box 222:3746)
    - Meunier, Emile, 1947 (Box 222:3747)
    - Michaud, Alexander, 1956 (Box 222:3748)
    - Michon, Lea, 1952 (Box 222:3749)
    - Milette, Albert A., 1946 (Box 222:3750)
    - Milhomme, Oswald J., 1942 (Box 222:3751)
    - Millard, Nelson, 1953 (Box 222:3752)
    - Miller, Aino, 1951 (Box 222:3753)
    - Miller, Daniel, 1951 (Box 222:3754)
    - Miller, Gertrude, 1946 (Box 222:3755)
    - Miller, Raymond, 1951 (Box 222:3756)
    - Millette, Cecile, 1954 (Box 222:3757)
    - Milliord, Nelson J., Jr., 1937 (Box 222:3758)
    - Mineau, Albert J., 1951 (Box 222:3759)
    - Mineau, Henry, 1951 (Box 222:3760)
    - Mineau, Irene Jarvis, 1951 (Box 222:3761)
    - Mineau, Theresa F., 1951 (Box 222:3762)
    - Miner, Albert, 1955 (Box 222:3763)
    - Minior, Maryon J., 1937 (Box 222:3764)
    - Misiaszek, Agata, 1941 (Box 222:3765)
    - Miskiewicz, John, 1938 (Box 222:3766)
    - Miskiewicz, Stanley, 1941 (Box 222:3767)
    - Mitchell, Alexander N., 1941 (Box 222:3768)
    - Mitchell, Bernard, 1957 (Box 222:3769)
    - Mitchell, Clifford, 1938 (Box 222:3770)
    - Mitchell, Earl C., 1937 (Box 222:3771)
    - Moffitt, Allen A., 1937 (Box 222:3772)
    - Moffitt, Edward, 1942 (Box 222:3773)
    - Moffitt, Loretta K. D., 1941 (Box 222:3774)
    - Moffitt, Myron M., 1941 (Box 222:3775)
    - Moffitt, Walter Russell, 1941 (Box 222:3776)
    - Moffitt, William S., 1938 (Box 222:3777)
    - Moisan, Antoinette, 1945 (Box 222:3778)
    - Moisan, Antoinette B., 1955 (Box 222:3779)
    - Mokrzcki, Lawrence J., 1939 (Box 222:3780)
    - Molinski, Kiejdy Cajda, 1956 (Box 222:3781)
    - Molinski, Mary, 1949 (Box 222:3782)
    - Molloy, Elizabeth, 1943 (Box 222:3783)
    - Monahan, Francis J., 1945 (Box 222:3784)
    - Monahan, Priscilla, 1947 (Box 222:3785)
    - Monahan, Terrence, 1947 (Box 222:3786)
    - Mondor, Louis J., 1952 (Box 222:3787)
    - Mongeau, Alexandrine D., 1939 (Box 222:3788)
    - Mongeau, Henry, 1954 (Box 222:3789)
    - Mongeau, Henry N., 1942 (Box 222:3790)
    - Mongeau, Napoleon J., 1944 (Box 222:3791)
    - Montcalm, Thomas, 1955 (Box 229:5134)
    - Monty, Arthur O., 1953 (Box 222:3792)
    - Monville, Peter, 1939 (Box 222:3793)
    - Moore, Benjamin H., 1947 (Box 222:3794)
    - Moore, Paul, 1956 (Box 222:3795)
    - Moran, Beatrice B., 1952 (Box 222:3796)
    - Moran, Delvina, 1947 (Box 222:3797)
    - Moran, George T., 1953 (Box 222:3798)
    - Moran, Gladys, 1942 (Box 222:3799)
    - Moran, Lillian Mary, 1951 (Box 222:3800)
    - Moran, Mary E., 1955 (Box 222:3801)
    - Moran, Sophia L., 1953 (Box 222:3802)
    - Moran, Walter, 1955 (Box 222:3803)
    - Moran, Winfield Ellsworth, 1951 (Box 222:3804)
    - Moreau, Laura E., 1941 (Box 222:3805)
    - Moreau, Loretta F., 1940 (Box 222:3806)
    - Moreau, Ovide, 1942 (Box 222:3807)
    - Moreau, Winfred X., 1949 (Box 222:3808)
    - Moreira, Joseph S., 1940 (Box 222:3809)
    - Morel, Marcel, 1957 (Box 222:3810)
    - Morgan, Clarence, 1942 (Box 222:3811)
    - Morin, Anita, 1948 (Box 222:3812)
    - Morin, Elsie E. Johnson, 1951 (Box 222:3813)
    - Morin, Emile, 1956 (Box 222:3814)
    - Morin, Ernest J., 1955 (Box 222:3815)
    - Morin, Euclide, 1948 (Box 222:3816)
    - Morin, Gerard J., 1942 (Box 222:3817)
    - Morin, Israel J., 1953 (Box 222:3818)
    - Morin, Lionel J., 1952 (Box 222:3819)
    - Morin, Nellie, 1954 (Box 222:2820)
    - Morin, Rita D. Laflamme, 1946 (Box 222:3821)
    - Morin, Roger, 1954 (Box 222:3822)
    - Morin, Romeo, 1957 (Box 222:3823)
    - Morin, Romeo, Jr., 1956 (Box 222:3824)
    - Morin, Ulde J., 1940 (Box 222:3825)
    - Morin, Wilfred, 1956 (Box 222:3826)
    - Morneau, Servule J., 1953 (Box 222:3827)
    - Morris, Abel R., 1944 (Box 222:3828)
    - Morris, Eva, 1956 (Box 222:3829)
    - Morris, Richard Joseph, 1946 (Box 222:3830)
    - Morrison, Emma, 1942 (Box 222:3831)
    - Morrison, William E., 1942 (Box 222:3832)
    - Morrissey, Annue Rose, 1945 (Box 222:3833)
    - Morissette, Joseph E., 1953 (Box 222:3834)
    - Morrissette, Juliette, 19 (Box 222:3835)
    - Morrissette, Roger C., 1950 (Box 222:3836)
    - Morse, Alice L., 1941 (Box 222:3837)
    - Morse, Armand, 1950 (Box 222:3838)
    - Morse, Edgar J., 1939 (Box 222:3839)
    - Morse, Estelle Boucher, 1942 (Box 222:3840)
    - Morse, Henry E., 1937 (Box 222:3841)
    - Morse, Marjorie, 1956 (Box 222:3842)
    - Morse, Orrin H., 1937 (Box 222:3843)
    - Morse, Oscar, 1938 (Box 222:3844)
    - Morse, Stella N., 1943 (Box 222:3845)
    - Mortimer, Beatrice, 1956 (Box 222:3846)
    - Mosher, Allan E., 1945 (Box 222:3847)
    - Mosher, Marie D., 1958 (Box 222:3848)
    - Moulin, Eugene, 1955 (Box 222:3849)
    - Moyen, Joseph Fabien, 1950 (Box 222:3850)
    - Mullien, Robert, 1955 (Box 223:3851)
    - Munro, Arthur, 1953 (Box 223:3852)
    - Mureault, Mary B., 1940 (Box 223:3853)
    - Murphy, Violet T., 1939 (Box 223:3854)
    - Murray, Frank, 1952 (Box 223:3855)
    - Murray, Katherine, 1937 (Box 223:3956)
    - Murray, Marion P., 1957 (Box 223:3857)
    - Mutney, Mitchell, 1947 (Box 223:3858)
    - Myrteza, Kimal, 1957 (Box 223:3859)
    - MacDonald, John, 1951 (Box 223:3860)
    - MacKenzie, Kathryn, 1942 (Box 223:3861)
    - MacRoae, Roderick, 1951 (Box 223:3862)
    - McCartney, Agatha, 1954 (Box 223:3863)
    - McClure, Donald H., 1954 (Box 223:3864)
    - McCormack, Michael J., 1941 (Box 223:3865)
    - McCormack, Teresa Corene, 1941 (Box 223:3866)
    - McCoy, Charles William, Jr., 1953 (Box 223:3867)
    - McCoy, Michael, 1942 (Box 223:3868)
    - McDonald, Richard L., 19 (Box 223:3869)
    - McFarlane, Louis, 1950 (Box 223:3870)
    - McGee, Lida, 1940 (Box 223:3871)
    - McGovern, Elizabeth, 1953 (Box 223:3872)
    - McKenna, Albert G., 1937 (Box 223:3873)
    - McKenna, Arthur E., 1938 (Box 223:3874)
    - McKenna, Cormick P., 1938 (Box 223:3875)
    - McKenney, Pearl Hope, 1945 (Box 223:3876)
    - McLaughlin, Jeannette, 1948 (Box 223:3877)
    - McMerriman, Francis J., 1942 (Box 223:3878)
    - McShane, Irving Armstrong, 1954 (Box 223:3879)
    - Nadeau, Dora, 1955 (Box 223:3880)
    - Nash, Ethel, 1954 (Box 223:3881)
    - Nash, George, 1954 (Box 223:3882)
    - Natorski, John, 1956 (Box 223:3883)
    - Naum, Blaga, 1956 (Box 223:3884)
    - Nelson, Delbert, 1957 (Box 223:3885)
    - Nelson, John, 1946 (Box 223:3886)
    - Nelson, John J., 1955 (Box 223:3887)
    - Nelson, Marion, 1948 (Box 223:3888)
    - Nelson, Mildred, 1945 (Box 223:3889)
    - Nelson, Raymond, 1953 (Box 223:3890)
    - Nescior, John, 1941 (Box 223:3891)
    - Neustaetter, Fritz, 1937 (Box 223:3892)
    - Neveu, Euclid U., 1937 (Box 223:3893)
    - Newcombe, Charles, 1954 (Box 223:3894)
    - Newcomb, Everett W., 1953 (Box 223:3895)
    - Newman, Wallace, 1956 (Box 223:3896)
    - Newport, Winfred E., 1952 (Box 223:3897)
    - Newton, Hebert C., 1942 (Box 223:3898)
    - Nichols, Georgianna, 1951 (Box 223:3899)
    - Nicolosi, Agatino, 1943 (Box 223:3900)
    - Nicolosi, John, 1943 (Box 223:3901)
    - Nicolosi, Joseph A., 1943 (Box 223:3902)
    - Nicolosi, Lucy, 1943 (Box 223:3903)
    - Niejadlik, Victoria W., 1941 (Box 223:3904)
    - Nielson, Jacqueline, 1955 (Box 223:3905)
    - Nimmo, John, 1942 (Box 223:3906)
    - Ninteau, Eugene, 1949 (Box 223:3907)
    - Noble, John J., 1950 (Box 223:3908)
    - Noble, William J., 1950 (Box 223:3909)
    - Noistering, Joseph, 1941 (Box 223:3910)
    - Nollet, Lucien, 1950 (Box 223:3911)
    - Nolte, Herman, 1950 (Box 223:3912)
    - Nordberg, Helmer, 1949 (Box 223:3913)
    - Nordberg, Lorena Ouillette, 1951 (Box 223:3914)
    - Normandie, Blanche, 1937 (Box 223:3915)
    - Normandin, Raymond, 1945 (Box 223:3916)
    - Normandin, Virginia, 1945 (Box 223:3917)
    - Nowicki, Kamelia, 1940 (Box 223:3918)
    - Nowicki, Stanley J., 1940 (Box 223:3919)
    - Nye, Lillian M. Carr, 1948 (Box 223:3920)
    - oates, Charles F., 1942 (Box 223:3921)
    - Oates, Eva, 1951 (Box 223:3922)
    - Oates, Thelma M. H., 1941 (Box 223:3923)
    - O'Brien, Madeline M., 1948 (Box 223:3924)
    - O'Clair, Laura G., 1950 (Box 223:3925)
    - O'Connell, Rita A., 1950 (Box 223:3926)
    - O'Connor, James, 1942 (Box 223:3927)
    - Ogara, Lawrence, 1939 (Box 223:3928)
    - Oja, Frank N., 1953 (Box 223:3929)
    - O'Keefe, Bernice Boothman, 1941 (Box 223:3930)
    - Oksanen, Owney D., 1940 (Box 223:3931)
    - Olado, Helen, 1942 (Box 223:3932)
    - Oliverio, Laura S., 1939 (Box 223:3933)
    - Opperman, Ernest, 1948 (Box 223:3934)
    - Orzech, Charles, Jr., 1945 (Box 223:3935)
    - Osga, Blanche, 1951 (Box 223:3936)
    - Osiper, George, 1951 (Box 223:3937)
    - Ouellette, Alphonse J., 1942 (Box 223:3938)
    - Ouellette, Evelyn D., 1942 (Box 223:3939)
    - Ouellette, Rita J., 1939 (Box 223:3940)
    - Ouillett, Armand, 1950 (Box 223:3941)
    - Ouillette, Mary G., 1949 (Box 223:3942)
    - Ouillette, Rosario, 1957 (Box 223:3943)
    - Ouimette, Narcisse, 1937 (Box 223:3944)
    - Pacheco, Eleanor, 1942 (Box 223:3945)
    - Pacheco, Louis, Jr., 1941 (Box 223:3946)
    - Page, George S., 1952 (Box 223:3947)
    - Page, Jeannette, 1955 (Box 223:3948)
    - Page, Leo W., 1952 (Box 223:3949)
    - Pagnano, Edward J., 1941 (Box 223:3950)
    - Pagnano, Frances, 1941 (Box 223:3951)
    - Pagnano, Rocco V., 1941 (Box 223:3952)
    - Paine, Frank, 1942 (Box 223:3953)
    - Panek, Frank, 1954 (Box 223:3954)
    - Panek, Mary O., 1950 (Box 223:3955)
    - Panteleakos, Foto B., 1953 (Box 223:3956)
    - Panu, Zurica, 1955 (Box 223:3957)
    - Papalion, John Francis, 1941 (Box 223:3958)
    - Papini, Steisia, 1952 (Box 223:3959)
    - Pappas, Charles, 1951 (Box 223:3960)
    - Pappas, Peter K., 1952 (Box 223:3961)
    - Pappas, Theodore C., 1940 (Box 223:3962)
    - Paprawa, John S., 1943 (Box 223:3963)
    - Paquette, Alice Madon, 1955 (Box 223:3964)
    - Paquette, Cordelia H., 1944 (Box 223:3965)
    - Paquette, Donat N., 1951 (Box 223:3966)
    - Paquette, Edward, 1943 (Box 223:3967)
    - Paquette, Gerard J., 1948 (Box 223:3968)
    - Paquette, Norman Chester, 1941 (Box 223:3969)
    - Paquette, Raymond, 1943 (Box 223:3970)
    - Paquette, Rudolph A., 1951 (Box 223:3971)
    - Paquette, Wilfred D., 1944 (Box 223:3972)
    - Paquin, Emma, 1955 (Box 223:3973)
    - Paquin, Joseph A., 1937 (Box 223:3974)
    - Paquin, Lawrence A., 1937 (Box 223:3975)
    - Paquin, Mary A., 1954 (Box 223:3976)
    - Paquin, Violette St. Germain, 1957 (Box 223:3977)
    - Paradis, Emanuella V., 1939 (Box 223:3978)
    - Parent, Albina N., 1938 (Box 223:3979)
    - Parent, Alfred J., 1952 (Box 223:3980)
    - Parent, Armand E., 1937 (Box 223:3981)
    - Parent, Dorothy M., 1942 (Box 223:3982)
    - Parent, Josephine B., 1953 (Box 223:3983)